export const questions = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: "Which city is the capital of Australia?",
        options: ["Sydney", "Melbourne", "Canberra"],
        answer: "Canberra",
        explanation: "Canberra was selected as the capital in 1908 as a compromise between rivals Sydney and Melbourne."
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: "Which country is home to the city of Marrakech?",
        options: ["Morocco", "Tunisia", "Egypt"],
        answer: "Morocco",
        explanation: "Marrakech is a major economic center and home to mosques, palaces, and gardens."
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: "In which country will you find the city of Kyoto?",
        options: ["South Korea", "Japan", "China"],
        answer: "Japan",
        explanation: "Kyoto was the capital of Japan for more than one thousand years."
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: "Which city is famously known as the “City of Love”?",
        options: ["Rome", "Vienna", "Paris"],
        answer: "Paris",
        explanation: "Paris is often referred to as the \"City of Love\" because of its romantic atmosphere and landmarks."
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: "Lagos is located in which country?",
        options: ["Ghana", "Kenya", "Nigeria"],
        answer: "Nigeria",
        explanation: "Lagos is the most populous city in Nigeria and the African continent."
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: "Which city is the capital of Canada?",
        options: ["Toronto", "Vancouver", "Ottawa"],
        answer: "Ottawa",
        explanation: "Ottawa was chosen as the capital of Canada by Queen Victoria in 1857."
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: "Where is the city of Buenos Aires located?",
        options: ["Chile", "Argentina", "Brazil"],
        answer: "Argentina",
        explanation: "Buenos Aires is the capital and primate city of Argentina."
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: "Which city is the capital of Egypt?",
        options: ["Alexandria", "Giza", "Cairo"],
        answer: "Cairo",
        explanation: "Cairo is the capital of Egypt and the largest city in the Arab world."
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: "In which country will you find the city of Auckland?",
        options: ["Australia", "New Zealand", "Fiji"],
        answer: "New Zealand",
        explanation: "Auckland is the largest city in New Zealand, known as the \"City of Sails\"."
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: "Which African city is famous for Table Mountain?",
        options: ["Accra", "Cairo", "Cape Town"],
        answer: "Cape Town",
        explanation: "Table Mountain is a flat-topped mountain forming a prominent landmark overlooking the city of Cape Town."
    }
];
